

07 Gbede Street, Bickersteth Estate, lwaya,Lagos. 08126477066 tonyobi98@gmail.com

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Creative and strategic Marketing and Public Relations specialist offering expertise in social media management, media relations, partaking in Marketing and PR campaigns. I enjoy creative problem solving and getting exposure on multiple projects. I will excel in the collaborative environment of your company. I am a team player who offers creativity and professionalism.

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- · Market research
- Brand management
- Promotional campaigns
- Social Media Marketing
- Search Engine Optimisation
- · Search Engine Marketing
- · Digital marketing

- Advertising coordination
- Product Development
- Customer Management
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Social Media Management
- Google Analytics/Adwords
- CRM Tools

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Marketing and Public Relations Manager

### Radeus Business Technology

April 2022 - February 2023

- Developing and implementing marketing strategies for new products
- · Developed and led team's efforts to increase online presence
- Planning, directing and executing corporates events
- In charge of handling and maintaining relations with clients
- Confer with production, graphic design and web-design personnel to coordinate production of corporate communications materials
- · Developing and implementing public relations strategies
- · Analysing marketing performance using different metrics and tools available

#### Marketing Manager

### Gemnita Hair

### January 2021- February 2022

- Developed marketing strategies and campaigns to promote the brand
- Analysed data and metrics to evaluate the effectiveness of marketing campaigns and refine strategies accordingly.
- · Collaborated with other teams to develop integrated marketing campaigns
- Conducted market research to identify consumer needs, preferences, and behaviours
- Implemented strategies that grew total following to 12k followers , which simultaneously increased sales volume
- Analysed market trends and consumer behavior to develop marketing campaigns that resonate with the target audience

## Social Media Manager

## Kunmi Exchange

May 2020 - January 2021

- Created the content calendar across the social platform to coincide with new marketing strategies
- · Completed competitive research and benchmarking to further understand target audience and goals
- · Monitor online presence of company's brand and engage with users, strengthening customer relationship
- · Analysed and reported social media and online marketing campaign result

# **Public Relations Executive Intern**

#### Media Panache

November 2019 - February 2020

- Used risk analysis tools and management approaches in a consistent manner for clients
- Sent press release statements to the media outlets for clients
- Created the content calendar across the social platform to coincide with new marketing strategies
- Created PR campaigns for clients
- · Completed competitive research and benchmarking to further understand target audience and goals

## **EDUCATION**

## **CERTIFICATION**

## **University of Lagos**

Fundamentals of digital marketing Bachelor of Science [B.Sc] - Mass Communication Major in Public Relations and Advertising 2016 - 2020 Google Digital marketing Skills